AS YOU STOOD BY
EUN-SU, HUI-SU AND JIN-YOUNG
Jesus.
I could really use a ride.
Where are you headed?
DETECTIVE KANG JU-YEON
I'm driving.
I'll call you back.
DETECTIVE KANG JU-YEON
CALL ENDED
SEOUL SEOCHO POLICE STATION
- Ah!
- Who are you?
Fuck!
Ah!
- Who the hell are you?
- Bitch!
I'm not telling you shit.
Ah!
Fuck! Get lost!
Stop!
You know me? How's that?
And you?
How'd you manage to track me down?
Did Jo Eun-su try to recruit you too?
Jo Eun-su?
Shit!
Why are you cuffing me?
I haven't done anything wrong.
Shit.
You can't do this to me! Let me go!
- Shit.
- Let me go, dammit.
You hear me?
Get these fucking things off me.
Jin-pyo?
Why do you have my brother's phone?
I found it.
What, is that a crime now?
Fuck.
Hey! Don't! Fuck!
Get off my phone.
I said get off my fucking phone!
JO HUI-SU
Hui-su?
How do you know Hui-su?
Why did you call her?
Uncuff me, and we can talk.
Extorting my mother
and blackmailing Hui-su?
Why do that?
Jin-pyo put you up to it?
Oh shit, man.
You don't know shit.
Huh?
The caller you are trying
to reach is unavailable.
Are you still at work?
Why aren't you picking up?
If Jang Kang calls today,
just don't pick up.
I'm gonna meet him and settle this.
JO HUI-SU
Hello?
Mr. Jang, this is Hui-su.
MR. JIN SO-BAEK
Yes, Mr. Jin?
It's urgent. I need you.
Get to the warehouse as soon as you can.
Eun-su is on her way here too.
Thirty minutes, Detective.
That's the most I can give you.
A tattoo?
Why do you have
my brother's phone?
That's not Jin-pyo at the airport at all.
Somebody switched the luggage.
Jesus Christ.
Is he in there?
JO EUN-SU
Oh wow.
Noh Jin-pyo.
- He's here, isn't he?
Huh?
So they were friends?
Idiot.
It was you. Wasn't it?
You did it.
You killed my brother.
Fortunately,
it's just a flesh wound.
It should heal up fine.
So I'll be on my way.
Thank you, Doctor.
I'm sorry.
He could've killed you.
You know how dangerous he is,
and you still went and did that?
I guess I got cocky.
And it almost got you killed!
What if I'd lost you?
After what you did to save me from him.
It wasn't only about helping you though.
There are so many things
I've avoided in my life.
When I was little,
it was all I'd ever known.
Just part of childhood.
And as my dad got older,
I thought he'd calm down
and stop the abuse.
And when I realized
he was still hurting her, I ignored it.
I was afraid I'd lose the life
I'd built here and get sucked back in.
So I pretended not to know.
But with everything that led
to Mrs. Kang killing herself, I realized...
DEARLY DEPARTED MS. KANG HUI-YEON
...if I don't break the cycle,
it will never end.
That's why I did it.
It wasn't just for you.
I needed to break it for me too.
You don't have to carry all the weight.
Are you in pain?
Why? Does it look bad?
Not with the bandage.
It's fine.
It's times like these,
you gotta break out the strong stuff.
Steer clear of Jang Kang from now on.
How did you know?
Is there anything
I don't know around here?
I know what you've been up to and that
you're in deeper than you can handle.
Hmm?
I'm surprised you got this far
without getting caught.
Those memories will always
come back to haunt you,
no matter how far you try to run.
That happened 20 years ago,
but sometimes I feel like
I'm still covered in blood.
You know, what you two did
is kind of admirable in a way.
I had a chance to see some things
on your husband's phone.
Son of a bitch got exactly
what he deserved.
I'll send Jang back to Shanghai.
What?
- It's not your problem though.
- You don't stand a chance against the guy.
Okay? He was a stowaway who survived
the roughest slums in China.
He's cunning, and he even managed
to pull one over on me,
and I'm a tough one to fool.
It's only fitting
that I put him in his place.
He's not only cunning, he's vicious.
He won't go down without a fight,
and you don't back down.
I backed down the first time
you showed up here, didn't I?
You're being overly protective,
and I appreciate it--
Then appreciate it.
Do as I say, and it'll be over.
- This is my fault and my problem to solve.
- Enough.
You're on my payroll.
And your friend could be on it soon.
So just accept the fact
that I'm gonna help you.
Jang Kang was nowhere to be found.
And then there's the other car.
When she took the exit all of a sudden,
I thought maybe
she wasn't tailing us after all.
But then she came back.
She drove right past me on that road.
Try running the plate number.
And send someone to watch
where Jang's staying.
Huh?
Uh-huh.
We found your phone.
That's a relief.
When you were driving last night,
did you happen to notice
anyone following you?
PSYCHOTROPIC DRUG
ZOLPIDEM
Where are we?
Jang Kang.
Did you make copies of what you saw
on Jin-pyo's phone? Yes or no.
Ah...
Your brother's missing,
and that's your first question?
Did you make any or not?
I'd start talking if I were you.
I know you murdered that security guard.
No, I didn't.
Noh Jin-pyo did that.
Why'd you do that?
Are there any copies?
No, there aren't.
Good boy. That wasn't so hard, was it?
THE FIRST FEMALE COMMISSIONER GENERAL
NOH JIN-YOUNG!
Jin-young.
Hi, did I wake you?
Jin-pyo.
Do you have news?
I think we're close.
Are you drinking again?
Ah, of course not.
I only finished the few drops
that were left from the last bottle.
Go ahead.
Turn the place upside down.
You won't find any.
I made your last DUI go away.
- Remember?
- I know.
I need to borrow your car for a while.
Mine's got a weird noise going on.
The garage at my place
is under renovation,
so I need to leave it here.
It smells awful
from the scenes I've been working.
So stay out of the garage for now.
All right?
MOVING SELECTED ITEMS TO TRASH
NO PHOTOS OR VIDEOS
LICENSE PLATE SEARCH RESULTS
LICENSE PLATE: 13M 6925
NAME: NOH JIN-YOUNG
Noh Jin-young.
You said your husband's name
is Jin-pyo, right?
And his sister is Jin-young?
How do you know Jin-young?
So the car
that was following me last night...
It was Noh Jin-young's.
And Mr. Ma says he saw this car
when Jang Kang got into yours.
Noh Jin-young knew he was there
when she followed you.
I don't see how Jin-young could have known
who Eun-su or Jang Kang were.
She hasn't come over lately,
and we haven't talked either.
But she's a cop.
MA HAE-RYONG
Oh, really?
I think she would have called you first
if she'd known anything about Jang.
But she didn't call me.
And I thought for sure Jang would call me
after what went down yesterday,
but he hasn't called either.
I... kinda panicked and called him
when I couldn't reach you last night.
He answered but hung up
without saying anything.
Given that neither one's gotten in touch,
I'd say she's got him.
I look forward to working with you.
So welcome aboard.
You won't be disappointed.
I trust your skills.
But since this is your first posting here,
I'll give you some valuable advice.
Please.
Your friends and family,
you better watch them like a hawk
if you wanna stay.
No matter how capable you are,
if their behavior
tarnishes your reputation,
your days here are over.
I'll make sure to do that.
OFFICE OF THE PRESIDENT
OF THE REPUBLIC OF KOREA
Jin-pyo's already dead.
There's nothing I can do
to change that math.
But maybe I can rewrite
the equation.
15th floor.
Eun-su?
Sounds like you were expecting someone.
Uh, just one of my neighbors
who left her colander here.
Eun-su.
Eun-su?
Sorry. I thought you were someone else.
LEE HYEON-JI
When did this blood get here?
Welcome to Lavie.
Oh, the most doting husband
with excellent taste.
Would you testify to that under oath?
Sorry?
Could I get the new catalogue
for the spring collection, please?
Getting your wife
expensive jewelry doesn't necessarily mean
you love her.
It could just be a matter
of trying to buy forgiveness.
Huh? Go ahead.
It looks like Jin-young knows
about Jang Kang and her brother.
MOTHER
Our specials today
are white ragù and truffle paccheri.
Mm-hmm.
My daughter-in-law will be happy.
Those are her two favorites.
We'll have one of each, please.
Of course.
How are you?
Jin-pyo.
He's back, I guess.
What?
Jin-pyo... has returned.
Is he at work?
You knew?
Weren't you going to tell me
about my son's return?
You knew... what he was doing?
All these years I suffered,
and you never brought it up.
- And now you acknowledge it so casually?
- I don't have time for your nonsense.
If you're going to manipulate Jin-pyo
into begging me for money
dressed like a vagrant again,
set him free.
I'll care for my son.
Noh Jin-young knew he was there
when she followed you.
Hi, how are you?
We really need to talk.
Why didn't you call first?
You were caught on a dashcam.
You know that?
What?
I saw footage of you on someone's dashcam.
From the time
the security guard was murdered.
A resident drove past the scene.
I had forgotten something
in the car that day.
Maybe, but you're not the only one
in the footage.
It appears my brother
was down there too.
He's still gone.
So he wasn't there.
It'd be impossible.
But then again, Mom has started saying
impossible things too.
She'll tell me she saw Jin-pyo,
and then take it back.
"Never mind.
Just wishful thinking," she says.
So I thought
maybe I should ask you.
About what?
Hui-su.
Where the fuck is he?
Jin-pyo is... in Shanghai, last I heard.
Yeah. That's right.
He took off on you.
But he'll be back eventually.
You know that, right?
Yes.
When?
She's driving her mother's car now?
And we're sure
she didn't hand him over to the police?
Mm-hmm.
Go to Ko Jeong-suk's for now.
Yes.
Jin-young's mother.
- That's Ko Jeong-suk?
- Yeah, you know her?
Jin-young needs a clean family record.
She wants a position
on the Presidential detail,
so that would explain
why she's gone quiet.
Wow, another layer.
Until we know...
You think...
she could have hidden Jang in her car?
We'll wait for the call. Okay?
Let's just wait.
This is she.
Oh, the Lavie department store?
Yes.
They're beautiful.
- Please have a seat.
- Thank you.
First, I apologize for the short notice,
but it would be such an honor
to have you speak at our VVIP event.
I really appreciate your making the time
to see me, Mrs. Ko.
When my children were little,
there wasn't a single day
we didn't have fresh flowers in the house.
On the priority list,
flowers came before food.
I truly believe that both my children
grew up to be gentle and kindhearted
because they were always surrounded
by the peaceful beauty of flowers.
I see.
So, these VVIP customers...
Is there a theme for the day?
I feel so rude,
but would you please
excuse me for a moment?
I really need to take this.
Of course.
Yes, I'm at a meeting
with our future guest speaker.
Jang Kang.
This is Eun-su. I'll get you out of there.
Come on.
Jang Kang!
Disable it before they send someone.
JO EUN-SU
There's something I think
I should tell you.
Hui-su thought the security guard
was spying on her.
She wanted to file a complaint,
but I convinced her not to.
But apparently, she threatened him anyway
without proof.
What kind of bothers me
is that man's the one who got killed.
Caught my attention,
which is why I rushed over there that day.
Oh, right.
We questioned a couple at the scene.
They left the garage
around the time of the crime,
and luckily, your sister-in-law
was cleared by their statement.
Hmm.
That is lucky.
Oh. I wanted to thank you.
For not mentioning her visit,
that day she came in.
Sorry?
Ah. You don't have to thank me for that.
She has serious issues.
She, uh,
hurts herself and pretends
that someone else did it.
She's going to try
to pin my brother for abuse,
but she saw me and ran off.
You know what?
I've told you too much already.
I took up your whole break.
- I'll buy you a drink next time.
- Or coffee's fine too.
- Yeah.
- At your service.
Yeah?
When was this?
Damn it.
Shit.
- Jin-young.
- Mom.
- You didn't call the police, did you?
- Of course not. I waited for you.
- But you should check what's missing.
- We need to check the cameras first.
No, it was a woman who came here.
She... pretended she works at
that fancy department store.
She said she wanted me to give a speech.
- But it was a trick.
- Department store?
Do you mean Lavie?
Yes.
What the hell is wrong with you?
I had to do something.
Who knows what she would've done--
I told you I would take care of it.
Where were you planning to go?
Were you just gonna keep driving
till you figured it out?
How long were you gonna drive?
I assume you have some kind of plan,
since you took him?
You trying to get hurt?
'Cause that's how you're acting!
JINGANG CHINESE MARKET
Jang Kang is going back
on the first boat I can find.
Okay.
Noh Jin-pyo as well.
Huh?
Mr. Jin?
Noh Jin-pyo died.
He left for Shanghai
a month and a half ago,
and things went terribly wrong.
If you're doing all of this
because of what you said
when we were talking over soup,
you really don't have to at all
'cause I was so completely stressed out,
I don't remember a thing you said.
If Jin-pyo's still in Korea, then what?
If you have a better solution,
I'm listening.
Gangneung Chodang
Police report, 1999.
Ring a bell?
I got it here.
112 EMERGENCY CALL INCIDENT REPORT
You were eight at the time.
Can't believe this.
All I did was turn the volume up
to watch the wrestling on television.
Is that a crime now?
I bumped my face
cleaning the bathroom earlier.
We'll need to talk to
anyone else who's in the house.
It's okay. You can come out.
Hi.
Can you tell us if you heard anything
like fighting or yelling earlier?
I... I fell asleep. I didn't hear anything.
I was in the closet
with my brother.
We were there playing hide and seek.
You turned a blind eye
to your own family.
So why are you all of a sudden
meddling in someone else's?
Is this some kind of attempt
at alleviating your conscience?
If you thought
you'd come out of this a hero,
you thought wrong.
The only thing this is gonna get you...
is charged with murder.
We'll find out soon enough, won't we?
I don't need Jang Kang to put you two--
MR. JIN SO-BAEK
Your call cannot be completed.
Mr. Jin.
You're right.
Jin-pyo needs to die in China.
Just shut up!
Where's Jo Eun-su? Huh?
Get her in here!
Go get her!
I said shut it.
You'll be on the first boat
out of here tonight.
You don't give orders here!
Jo Hui-su.
She had been secretly siphoning off
her husband's money,
and when he found out,
she faked injuries to make it look like
he was abusing her.
Then she used it to blackmail him.
But that wasn't enough
to satisfy her greed.
So she recruited her best friend,
Jo Eun-su, to kill him.
Then they pretended
a loving husband had just run off.
Then buried him.
You're driving me nuts.
I need water, man! Please!
Sit up.
Take it easy.
Bastard!
When I get back,
first thing on my list is gonna be
to hunt down your entire family
and cut 'em into pieces.
After I tell them
it's because of you. Fuck!
Pull over.
So, uh...
good luck
and all that.
Crazy bitch.
I can take you to where he's buried.
Your sister-in-law
and her friend won't say shit.
So we dig up your brother.
And take 'em for all they've got.
How much do you want?
Three billion.
That's 100 million off for you.
Mm. Wait.
Come on.
Get in.
Well, fuck me.
Deal?
You really need to do this?
I hired the asshole.
WI CHUN-GIL
- Excellent work today.
- Thank you, ma'am.
- Good night.
Hi.
I'm heading over now.
Should I bring anything?
Oh, before I forget,
you need to find your passport.
Mm-hmm.
He says we should have them on us
just in case.
Another thing.
No, forget it. It can wait.
Mm-hmm.
Did you find a ship?
MR. JIN SO-BAEK
Go to the mah-jongg club with Hui-su.
Make sure you lock the door.
- Turn it around.
- Yes, sir.
Son of bitch. Where is he?
Fuck! Piece of shit!
Look!
I told you!
Holy shit.
Is that a fucking deer head?
This is the spot.
I know it.
And these are
the same trees.
Are you just gonna stand there? Fuck!
You need to help me dig this fucker up!
Oh shit. Fuck!
Looks like you
did find the spot.
MEDICAL CERTIFICATE OF BODILY HARM
JO HUI-SU
It was a clear case of domestic violence.
I encouraged her to report the abuse.
And you're sure about that?
Yes.
Ah, hello, ma'am.
I'm not sure you remember,
but we met once. I'm Officer Choi.
Officer Choi.
I'm here to get some more information
about the security guard's murder.
I see.
And I brought this.
MEDICAL CERTIFICATE OF BODILY HARM
- The door is open.
I... should've paid more attention
when you were at the station
and offered you more help.
It was my mistake.
Uh...
Maybe you want some water?
- Here you are.
- Oh.
Thank you, ma'am.
On the night in question,
you were picked up on someone's dashcam.
Pretty near the scene of the murder.
You were seen in the garage,
and I would like to know
what you were doing there.
There was something I needed in the car.
It says your car wasn't in the garage,
but in the outdoor near your building.
Where you usually park.
Um, I meant to say I was getting something
from my husband's car.
He always parks it down there.
He worries it'll get scratched
if it's outside.
Ah.
That's it for me.
If you think of anything, give me a call.
And I'll be back
if I need more information.
All right. Thank you.
Uh, one last thing.
Do you need help with anything?
Uh, no.
And my husband's traveling.
It's nice of you to ask.
SENTINEL STUDIO APARTMENT
JIN-YOUNG
Oh my God.
Eun-su.
JIN-YOUNG
Call Eun-su, and she dies.
Same goes for your dear mom
at the nursing home.
Eun-su had nothing to do with this.
It was all my doing.
And my mom doesn't...
Just leave my mom alone. I beg you.
Do you really think I believe
your best friend wasn't involved?
She went to my mother's house
and kidnapped Jang Kang from my car.
What?
Where is she now?
- Tell me what you did to Eun-su!
- I didn't do anything to her.
But I found Jang in a terrible state
and rescued him
after she left him for dead.
I don't believe you.
Why should I even listen to you?
Think of everything
your friend has done for you.
Jo Eun-su
is unstable.
Who knows what she'll do next?
But she'll stop at nothing to help you.
Am I wrong?
Kill yourself.
Tonight.
Then I'll let your accomplice
off the hook.
And leave your mom alone too.
I finally got the job
with the president's office.
- Do you think I want this to blow up?
It's not like my dead brother
will be back to testify, will he?
But one of you has to pay, right?
Now that his body's been found,
the clock is ticking.
Stop crying.
It'll be over real soon.
Just go quietly.
EUN-SU
Hey, Eun-su.
What happened to your forehead?
Oh, I tripped on the desk.
I actually did.
Making piles of all the things to sell.
Well, be more careful.
Next stop, mah-jongg club.
Mm. Let's go.
- Hui-su.
- I've been on edge, and I'm too stressed.
The clattering takes all of it away.
You should try.
Hmm.
Just like Mr. Jin.
Clatter, clatter.
Listen--
Do you remember
when we'd go to the Jungang Market
to get candied chicken
instead of going to study hall?
Masan granny's chicken?
Oh! Ah, such good memories.
I'm craving it right now.
You think it still exists? She was old.
Maybe. Or somebody else
may have taken it over.
Now I'm curious.
She still has it.
There's even a picture of her. Look.
Almost all five-star reviews.
That's so cool.
We'll go there soon. My treat.
Okay.
You know, this made me hungry.
You want some soup?
So you put on lipstick before you eat now?
Just like the old days.
I just need to go to the bathroom.
Don't take too long,
or they're gonna get soggy.
Thank you, Eun-su.
Hurry up. I'm starving.
Mm.
EUN-SU
MOM
I'M SORRY TO LEAVE YOU ALL ALONE
I COMMITTED AN UNFORGIVABLE SIN
I KILLED JIN-PYO
EUN-SU